import React from 'react'
let signs = {
    title: "Signs",
    questions: [
        {
            question: "The Zodiac has this many signs",
            answers: ["8", "14", "12", "13"],
            correct: "12"
        },
        {
            question: "Each Zodiac sign was named after this",
            answers: ["Animals", "Myths", "Gods", "Constellations"],
            correct: "Constellations"
        },
        {
            question: "The word horoscope comes from Greek and means this",
            answers: ["Stars in heaven", "One who observes the hour", "Terrible destiny", "Future"],
            correct: "One who observes the hour"
        },
        {
            question: "Those born on New Year's day fall under this sign",
            answers: ["Sagittarius", "Cancer", "Capricorn", "Gemini"],
            correct: "Capricorn"
        },
        {
            question: "This Zodiac sign runs from Feb 20 until Mar 20",
            answers: ["Pisces", "Cancer", "Leo", "Taurus"],
            correct: "Pisces"
        },
        {
            question: "Those born on Valentine's day fall under this sign",
            answers: ["Pisces", "Aquarius", "Cancer", "Scorpio"],
            correct: "Aquarius"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is represented by the crab",
            answers: ["Cancer", "Aquarius", "Gemini", "Sagittarius"],
            correct: "Cancer"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is represented by the archer",
            answers: ["Scorpio", "Taurus", "Sagittarius", "Virgo"],
            correct: "Sagittarius"
        },
        {
            question: "This animal does not represent a Zodiac sign",
            answers: ["Bull", "Owl", "Scorpion", "Goat"],
            correct: "Owl"
        },
        {
            question: "Those born on Halloween day fall under this sign",
            answers: ["Taurus", "Gemini", "Virgo", "Scorpio"],
            correct: "Scorpio"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is represented by the twins",
            answers: ["Virgo", "Gemini", "Taurus", "Cancer"],
            correct: "Gemini"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is not a fire sign",
            answers: ["Virgo", "Ares", "Leo", "Sagittarius"],
            correct: "Virgo"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is not an earth sign",
            answers: ["Virgo", "Pisces", "Capricorn", "Taurus"],
            correct: "Pisces"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is not an air sign",
            answers: ["Leo", "Libra", "Gemini", "Aquarius"],
            correct: "Leo"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is not a water sign",
            answers: ["Scorpio", "Cancer", "Pisces", "Taurus"],
            correct: "Taurus"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign is represented by the scales",
            answers: ["Taurus", "Libra", "Virgo", "Aquarius"],
            correct: "Libra"
        },
        {
            question: "This sign runs from Mar 21 to Apr 20",
            answers: ["Aries", "Libra", "Virgo", "Cancer"],
            correct: "Aries"
        }
    ]
}

export default signs